[{"answer":{"answer":"First Name","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":1,"master_id":1,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"fname","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"MI","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":2,"master_id":2,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"mi","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Last Name","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":3,"master_id":3,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"lname","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Address","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":4,"master_id":4,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"address","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"City","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":5,"master_id":5,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"city","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"State","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":6,"master_id":6,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":6,"shortname":"st","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0106"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Zip","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":7,"master_id":7,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":7,"shortname":"zip","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0107"}},{"answer":{"answer":"County","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":8,"master_id":8,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":8,"shortname":"county","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0108"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Prim Phone","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":9,"master_id":9,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":9,"shortname":"phone1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0109"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Sec Phone","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":10,"master_id":10,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":10,"shortname":"phone2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0110"}},{"answer":{"answer":"eMail","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":11,"master_id":11,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":11,"shortname":"email","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0111"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Month of Birth","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":12,"master_id":12,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":12,"shortname":"mob","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0112"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Day of Birth","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":13,"master_id":13,"other_question":"","question_id":1,"requires_other":false,"sequence":13,"shortname":"dob","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"a0113"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":14,"master_id":14,"other_question":"What was your job?","question_id":2,"requires_other":true,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":15,"master_id":15,"other_question":"","question_id":2,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":16,"master_id":16,"other_question":"Enter name and relation?","question_id":3,"requires_other":true,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":17,"master_id":17,"other_question":"","question_id":3,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":18,"master_id":18,"other_question":"","question_id":4,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":19,"master_id":19,"other_question":"","question_id":4,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":20,"master_id":20,"other_question":"","question_id":5,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:15Z","id":21,"master_id":21,"other_question":"","question_id":5,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0402"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":22,"master_id":22,"other_question":"","question_id":6,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":23,"master_id":23,"other_question":"","question_id":6,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0502"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":24,"master_id":24,"other_question":"","question_id":7,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0601"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":25,"master_id":25,"other_question":"Enter work permit #","question_id":7,"requires_other":true,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0602"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":26,"master_id":26,"other_question":"","question_id":8,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0701"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":27,"master_id":27,"other_question":"","question_id":8,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0702"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":28,"master_id":28,"other_question":"","question_id":9,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0801"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":29,"master_id":29,"other_question":"","question_id":9,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0802"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":30,"master_id":30,"other_question":"","question_id":10,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g0901"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":31,"master_id":31,"other_question":"","question_id":10,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g0902"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":32,"master_id":32,"other_question":"","question_id":11,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g1001"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":33,"master_id":33,"other_question":"","question_id":11,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g1002"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":34,"master_id":34,"other_question":"","question_id":12,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g1101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":35,"master_id":35,"other_question":"","question_id":12,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:23Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g1102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":36,"master_id":36,"other_question":"","question_id":13,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g1201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":37,"master_id":37,"other_question":"","question_id":13,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g1202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":38,"master_id":38,"other_question":"","question_id":14,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"g1301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":39,"master_id":39,"other_question":"","question_id":14,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"g1302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I did not complete high school and do not have a diploma or GED.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":40,"master_id":40,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"No Diploma/GED","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"e0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I did not complete high school but completed a non-diploma trade school.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":41,"master_id":41,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"Trade School","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"e0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I completed high school but did not graduate (obtained certificate).","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":42,"master_id":42,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"Certificate","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"e0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I completed high school through a GED program.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":43,"master_id":43,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"GED","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I completed high school and received a diploma.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":44,"master_id":44,"other_question":"Enter name of high school, city and state","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":5,"shortname":"HS Diploma","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"e0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I completed high school and received a diploma with a Career Tech Endorsement.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":45,"master_id":45,"other_question":"Enter name of high school, city and state","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":6,"shortname":"HS Diploma/CT","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"e0106"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I completed a military technical school.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":46,"master_id":46,"other_question":"Enter Technical Area","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":7,"shortname":"Military Tech","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0107"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I attended an associate\u2019s degree granting technical school/community college b","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":47,"master_id":47,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":8,"shortname":"Some Assoc","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0108"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I received an associate\u2019s degree from a technical school/community college.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":48,"master_id":48,"other_question":"Enter degree, institute, and year completed","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":9,"shortname":"Assoc Degree","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"e0109"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I attended an accredited, degree-granting college/university but did not receive","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":49,"master_id":49,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":10,"shortname":"Some College","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0110"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I received a BS/BA degree from an accredited, degree-granting college/university","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":50,"master_id":50,"other_question":"Enter degree, institute, and year completed","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":11,"shortname":"BS/BA Degree","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"e0111"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I attended an advanced degree program (MS/MA/PhD) but did receive a degree.","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":51,"master_id":51,"other_question":"","question_id":15,"requires_other":false,"sequence":12,"shortname":"Some Advanced","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0112"}},{"answer":{"answer":"I received an MS/MA/PhD degree from an accredited, degree-granting college/unive","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":52,"master_id":52,"other_question":"Enter degree, institute, and year completed","question_id":15,"requires_other":true,"sequence":13,"shortname":"MS/MA+ Degree","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"e0113"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Company","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":53,"master_id":53,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Company","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"City State","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":54,"master_id":54,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"City","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Job title/description","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":55,"master_id":55,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"Title","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"From (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":56,"master_id":56,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"From Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"To (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":57,"master_id":57,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"To Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Start Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":58,"master_id":58,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":6,"shortname":"Start Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0106"}},{"answer":{"answer":"End Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":59,"master_id":59,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":7,"shortname":"End Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0107"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Reason for leaving","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":60,"master_id":60,"other_question":"","question_id":16,"requires_other":false,"sequence":8,"shortname":"Leaving","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0108"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Company","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":61,"master_id":61,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Company","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"City State","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":62,"master_id":62,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"City","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Job title/description","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":63,"master_id":63,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"Title","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"From (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":64,"master_id":64,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"From Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"To (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":65,"master_id":65,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"To Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Start Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":66,"master_id":66,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":6,"shortname":"Start Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0206"}},{"answer":{"answer":"End Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":67,"master_id":67,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":7,"shortname":"End Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0207"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Reason for leaving","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":68,"master_id":68,"other_question":"","question_id":17,"requires_other":false,"sequence":8,"shortname":"Leaving","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0208"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Company","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":69,"master_id":69,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Company","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"City State","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:16Z","id":70,"master_id":70,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"City","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Job title/description","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":71,"master_id":71,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"Title","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"From (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":72,"master_id":72,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"From Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"To (YY/MM)","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":73,"master_id":73,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"To Date","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Start Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":74,"master_id":74,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":6,"shortname":"Start Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0306"}},{"answer":{"answer":"End Wage/Salary","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":75,"master_id":75,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":7,"shortname":"End Wage","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0307"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Reason for leaving","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":76,"master_id":76,"other_question":"","question_id":18,"requires_other":false,"sequence":8,"shortname":"Leaving","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0308"}},{"answer":{"answer":"","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":77,"master_id":77,"other_question":"","question_id":19,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"OtherExp","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"w0401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":78,"master_id":78,"other_question":"","question_id":20,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":79,"master_id":79,"other_question":"","question_id":20,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":80,"master_id":80,"other_question":"","question_id":20,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":81,"master_id":81,"other_question":"","question_id":20,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":82,"master_id":82,"other_question":"","question_id":20,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":83,"master_id":83,"other_question":"","question_id":21,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":84,"master_id":84,"other_question":"","question_id":21,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":85,"master_id":85,"other_question":"","question_id":21,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":86,"master_id":86,"other_question":"","question_id":21,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":87,"master_id":87,"other_question":"","question_id":21,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":88,"master_id":88,"other_question":"","question_id":22,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":89,"master_id":89,"other_question":"","question_id":22,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":90,"master_id":90,"other_question":"","question_id":22,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":91,"master_id":91,"other_question":"","question_id":22,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":92,"master_id":92,"other_question":"","question_id":22,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":93,"master_id":93,"other_question":"","question_id":23,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":94,"master_id":94,"other_question":"","question_id":23,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0402"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":95,"master_id":95,"other_question":"","question_id":23,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0403"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":96,"master_id":96,"other_question":"","question_id":23,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0404"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":97,"master_id":97,"other_question":"","question_id":23,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0405"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":98,"master_id":98,"other_question":"","question_id":24,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":99,"master_id":99,"other_question":"","question_id":24,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0502"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":100,"master_id":100,"other_question":"","question_id":24,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0503"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":101,"master_id":101,"other_question":"","question_id":24,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0504"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":102,"master_id":102,"other_question":"","question_id":24,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0505"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":103,"master_id":103,"other_question":"","question_id":25,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0601"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":104,"master_id":104,"other_question":"","question_id":25,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0602"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:17Z","id":105,"master_id":105,"other_question":"","question_id":25,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0603"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":106,"master_id":106,"other_question":"","question_id":25,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0604"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":107,"master_id":107,"other_question":"","question_id":25,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0605"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":108,"master_id":108,"other_question":"","question_id":26,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0701"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":109,"master_id":109,"other_question":"","question_id":26,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0702"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":110,"master_id":110,"other_question":"","question_id":26,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0703"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":111,"master_id":111,"other_question":"","question_id":26,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0704"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":112,"master_id":112,"other_question":"","question_id":26,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0705"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":113,"master_id":113,"other_question":"","question_id":27,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0801"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":114,"master_id":114,"other_question":"","question_id":27,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0802"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":115,"master_id":115,"other_question":"","question_id":27,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0803"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":116,"master_id":116,"other_question":"","question_id":27,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0804"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":117,"master_id":117,"other_question":"","question_id":27,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0805"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":118,"master_id":118,"other_question":"","question_id":28,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s0901"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":119,"master_id":119,"other_question":"","question_id":28,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s0902"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":120,"master_id":120,"other_question":"","question_id":28,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s0903"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":121,"master_id":121,"other_question":"","question_id":28,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s0904"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":122,"master_id":122,"other_question":"","question_id":28,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:24Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s0905"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":123,"master_id":123,"other_question":"","question_id":29,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1001"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":124,"master_id":124,"other_question":"","question_id":29,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1002"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":125,"master_id":125,"other_question":"","question_id":29,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1003"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":126,"master_id":126,"other_question":"","question_id":29,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1004"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":127,"master_id":127,"other_question":"","question_id":29,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1005"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":128,"master_id":128,"other_question":"","question_id":30,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":129,"master_id":129,"other_question":"","question_id":30,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:18Z","id":130,"master_id":130,"other_question":"","question_id":30,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":131,"master_id":131,"other_question":"","question_id":30,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":132,"master_id":132,"other_question":"","question_id":30,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":133,"master_id":133,"other_question":"","question_id":31,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":134,"master_id":134,"other_question":"","question_id":31,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":135,"master_id":135,"other_question":"","question_id":31,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":136,"master_id":136,"other_question":"","question_id":31,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":137,"master_id":137,"other_question":"","question_id":31,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":138,"master_id":138,"other_question":"","question_id":32,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":139,"master_id":139,"other_question":"","question_id":32,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":140,"master_id":140,"other_question":"","question_id":32,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":141,"master_id":141,"other_question":"","question_id":32,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":142,"master_id":142,"other_question":"","question_id":32,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":143,"master_id":143,"other_question":"","question_id":33,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":144,"master_id":144,"other_question":"","question_id":33,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1402"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":145,"master_id":145,"other_question":"","question_id":33,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1403"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":146,"master_id":146,"other_question":"","question_id":33,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1404"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":147,"master_id":147,"other_question":"","question_id":33,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1405"}},{"answer":{"answer":"0","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":148,"master_id":148,"other_question":"","question_id":34,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"s1501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":149,"master_id":149,"other_question":"","question_id":34,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"s1502"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:19Z","id":150,"master_id":150,"other_question":"","question_id":34,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"s1503"}},{"answer":{"answer":"6","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":151,"master_id":151,"other_question":"","question_id":34,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"s1504"}},{"answer":{"answer":"9","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":152,"master_id":152,"other_question":"","question_id":34,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"s1505"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No opinion","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":153,"master_id":153,"other_question":"","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"t0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Limited opinion","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":154,"master_id":154,"other_question":"","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Okay","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":155,"master_id":155,"other_question":"","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Great","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":156,"master_id":156,"other_question":"","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"t0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Weak","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":157,"master_id":157,"other_question":"What is missing?","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Crap","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":158,"master_id":158,"other_question":"What make it a crappy?","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":6,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"6.0","xml_key":"t0106"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Zilch ","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":159,"master_id":159,"other_question":"What make it a zilch?","question_id":35,"requires_other":false,"sequence":7,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"10.0","xml_key":"t0107"}},{"answer":{"answer":"GM","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":160,"master_id":160,"other_question":"","question_id":36,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Chrysler","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":161,"master_id":161,"other_question":"","question_id":36,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Ford","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":162,"master_id":162,"other_question":"Do you trust the Microsoft thingie?","question_id":36,"requires_other":true,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Slow","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":163,"master_id":163,"other_question":"","question_id":37,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Hard","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":164,"master_id":164,"other_question":"Tell me why hard is the best way?","question_id":37,"requires_other":true,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t0302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Fast","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":165,"master_id":165,"other_question":"","question_id":37,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Easy","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":166,"master_id":166,"other_question":"Tell me why easy is the best way?","question_id":37,"requires_other":true,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"t0304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"None","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":167,"master_id":167,"other_question":"","question_id":37,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"t0305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Enter text","answer_eval":"!(golf|fish|hunt)","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":168,"master_id":168,"other_question":"","question_id":38,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"hobbies","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t0401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"In one paragraph","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":169,"master_id":169,"other_question":"","question_id":39,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"none","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Steelers","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":170,"master_id":170,"other_question":"","question_id":40,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"t0601"}},{"answer":{"answer":"ASU","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":171,"master_id":171,"other_question":"","question_id":40,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"t0602"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Alabama","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":172,"master_id":172,"other_question":"","question_id":40,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0603"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Auburn","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":173,"master_id":173,"other_question":"","question_id":40,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0604"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Last Name","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":174,"master_id":174,"other_question":"","question_id":41,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Last Name","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0701"}},{"answer":{"answer":"First Name","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":175,"master_id":175,"other_question":"","question_id":41,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"First Name","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t0702"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Primary Phone","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":176,"master_id":176,"other_question":"","question_id":41,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"Primary Phone","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0703"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":177,"master_id":177,"other_question":"Why so low? Are you dumb?","question_id":42,"requires_other":true,"sequence":1,"shortname":"bad","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0801"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":178,"master_id":178,"other_question":"","question_id":42,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"poor","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t0802"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":179,"master_id":179,"other_question":"","question_id":42,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"fair","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0803"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":180,"master_id":180,"other_question":"","question_id":42,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"good","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"t0804"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":181,"master_id":181,"other_question":"","question_id":42,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"great","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"5.0","xml_key":"t0805"}},{"answer":{"answer":"The quick brown fox jumps the lazy dogs back. ","answer_eval":"1::back&1::fox&-0.5::dog&1::(quick|brown|lazy)","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:20Z","id":182,"master_id":182,"other_question":"","question_id":43,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Typing test","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"t0901"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Hint: It is bigger than 3 and smaller than 4.","answer_eval":"3.1415 .. 3.1415999","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":183,"master_id":183,"other_question":"","question_id":44,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t1001"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Yes","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":184,"master_id":184,"other_question":"","question_id":45,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"Y","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t1101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"No","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":185,"master_id":185,"other_question":"","question_id":45,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"N","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"t1102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":200,"master_id":200,"other_question":"","question_id":50,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":201,"master_id":201,"other_question":"","question_id":50,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":202,"master_id":202,"other_question":"","question_id":50,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":203,"master_id":203,"other_question":"","question_id":50,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":204,"master_id":204,"other_question":"","question_id":50,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":205,"master_id":205,"other_question":"","question_id":51,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":206,"master_id":206,"other_question":"","question_id":51,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":207,"master_id":207,"other_question":"","question_id":51,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":208,"master_id":208,"other_question":"","question_id":51,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":209,"master_id":209,"other_question":"","question_id":51,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":210,"master_id":210,"other_question":"","question_id":52,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":211,"master_id":211,"other_question":"","question_id":52,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":212,"master_id":212,"other_question":"","question_id":52,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":213,"master_id":213,"other_question":"","question_id":52,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":214,"master_id":214,"other_question":"","question_id":52,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":215,"master_id":215,"other_question":"","question_id":53,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":216,"master_id":216,"other_question":"","question_id":53,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0402"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":217,"master_id":217,"other_question":"","question_id":53,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0403"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":218,"master_id":218,"other_question":"","question_id":53,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0404"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":219,"master_id":219,"other_question":"","question_id":53,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0405"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":220,"master_id":220,"other_question":"","question_id":54,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":221,"master_id":221,"other_question":"","question_id":54,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0502"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":222,"master_id":222,"other_question":"","question_id":54,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0503"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":223,"master_id":223,"other_question":"","question_id":54,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0504"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":224,"master_id":224,"other_question":"","question_id":54,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0505"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":225,"master_id":225,"other_question":"","question_id":55,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0601"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:21Z","id":226,"master_id":226,"other_question":"","question_id":55,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0602"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":227,"master_id":227,"other_question":"","question_id":55,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0603"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":228,"master_id":228,"other_question":"","question_id":55,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0604"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":229,"master_id":229,"other_question":"","question_id":55,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0605"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":230,"master_id":230,"other_question":"","question_id":56,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0701"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":231,"master_id":231,"other_question":"","question_id":56,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0702"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":232,"master_id":232,"other_question":"","question_id":56,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0703"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":233,"master_id":233,"other_question":"","question_id":56,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0704"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":234,"master_id":234,"other_question":"","question_id":56,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0705"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":235,"master_id":235,"other_question":"","question_id":57,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0801"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":236,"master_id":236,"other_question":"","question_id":57,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0802"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":237,"master_id":237,"other_question":"","question_id":57,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0803"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":238,"master_id":238,"other_question":"","question_id":57,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0804"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":239,"master_id":239,"other_question":"","question_id":57,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0805"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":240,"master_id":240,"other_question":"","question_id":58,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i0901"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":241,"master_id":241,"other_question":"","question_id":58,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i0902"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":242,"master_id":242,"other_question":"","question_id":58,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i0903"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":243,"master_id":243,"other_question":"","question_id":58,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i0904"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":244,"master_id":244,"other_question":"","question_id":58,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i0905"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":245,"master_id":245,"other_question":"","question_id":59,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1001"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":246,"master_id":246,"other_question":"","question_id":59,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1002"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":247,"master_id":247,"other_question":"","question_id":59,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1003"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":248,"master_id":248,"other_question":"","question_id":59,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1004"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:22Z","id":249,"master_id":249,"other_question":"","question_id":59,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:26Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1005"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":250,"master_id":250,"other_question":"","question_id":60,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1101"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":251,"master_id":251,"other_question":"","question_id":60,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1102"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":252,"master_id":252,"other_question":"","question_id":60,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1103"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":253,"master_id":253,"other_question":"","question_id":60,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1104"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":254,"master_id":254,"other_question":"","question_id":60,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1105"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":255,"master_id":255,"other_question":"","question_id":61,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":256,"master_id":256,"other_question":"","question_id":61,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":257,"master_id":257,"other_question":"","question_id":61,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1203"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":258,"master_id":258,"other_question":"","question_id":61,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":259,"master_id":259,"other_question":"","question_id":61,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":260,"master_id":260,"other_question":"","question_id":62,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1301"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":261,"master_id":261,"other_question":"","question_id":62,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1302"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":262,"master_id":262,"other_question":"","question_id":62,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1303"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":263,"master_id":263,"other_question":"","question_id":62,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1304"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":264,"master_id":264,"other_question":"","question_id":62,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1305"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":265,"master_id":265,"other_question":"","question_id":63,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1401"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":266,"master_id":266,"other_question":"","question_id":63,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1402"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:23Z","id":267,"master_id":267,"other_question":"","question_id":63,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1403"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":268,"master_id":268,"other_question":"","question_id":63,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1404"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":269,"master_id":269,"other_question":"","question_id":63,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1405"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":270,"master_id":270,"other_question":"","question_id":64,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1501"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":271,"master_id":271,"other_question":"","question_id":64,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1502"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":272,"master_id":272,"other_question":"","question_id":64,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1503"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":273,"master_id":273,"other_question":"","question_id":64,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1504"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":274,"master_id":274,"other_question":"","question_id":64,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1505"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":275,"master_id":275,"other_question":"","question_id":65,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1601"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":276,"master_id":276,"other_question":"","question_id":65,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1602"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":277,"master_id":277,"other_question":"","question_id":65,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1603"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":278,"master_id":278,"other_question":"","question_id":65,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1604"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":279,"master_id":279,"other_question":"","question_id":65,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:36Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1605"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":280,"master_id":280,"other_question":"","question_id":66,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1701"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":281,"master_id":281,"other_question":"","question_id":66,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1702"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":282,"master_id":282,"other_question":"","question_id":66,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1703"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":283,"master_id":283,"other_question":"","question_id":66,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1704"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:24Z","id":284,"master_id":284,"other_question":"","question_id":66,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1705"}},{"answer":{"answer":"1","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":285,"master_id":285,"other_question":"","question_id":67,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1801"}},{"answer":{"answer":"2","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":286,"master_id":286,"other_question":"","question_id":67,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"2","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"i1802"}},{"answer":{"answer":"3","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":287,"master_id":287,"other_question":"","question_id":67,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"3","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"2.0","xml_key":"i1803"}},{"answer":{"answer":"4","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":288,"master_id":288,"other_question":"","question_id":67,"requires_other":false,"sequence":4,"shortname":"4","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"3.0","xml_key":"i1804"}},{"answer":{"answer":"5","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":289,"master_id":289,"other_question":"","question_id":67,"requires_other":false,"sequence":5,"shortname":"5","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"4.0","xml_key":"i1805"}},{"answer":{"answer":"","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":290,"master_id":290,"other_question":"","question_id":68,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i1901"}},{"answer":{"answer":"","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-12-04T11:21:25Z","id":291,"master_id":291,"other_question":"","question_id":69,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"1","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:17:37Z","value":"0.0","xml_key":"i2001"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Japanese","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-04-12T12:31:05Z","id":719,"master_id":0,"other_question":"Does you pedal stick to the metal?","question_id":36,"requires_other":true,"sequence":4,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0204"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Other","answer_eval":"","created_at":"2010-04-12T12:31:43Z","id":720,"master_id":0,"other_question":"Who made it?","question_id":36,"requires_other":true,"sequence":5,"shortname":"","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t0205"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Noun(s)","answer_eval":"fox&back","created_at":"2010-08-08T12:59:06Z","id":721,"master_id":0,"other_question":"","question_id":156,"requires_other":false,"sequence":1,"shortname":"nouns","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t1201"}},{"answer":{"answer":"Verb(s)","answer_eval":"jumps","created_at":"2010-08-08T12:59:55Z","id":722,"master_id":0,"other_question":"","question_id":156,"requires_other":false,"sequence":2,"shortname":"Verbs","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t1202"}},{"answer":{"answer":"At least one adjective","answer_eval":"(quick|brown|lazy)","created_at":"2010-08-08T13:01:20Z","id":723,"master_id":0,"other_question":"","question_id":156,"requires_other":false,"sequence":3,"shortname":"adjective","updated_at":"2010-12-20T23:15:25Z","value":"1.0","xml_key":"t1203"}}]